Bella@We really need to study it
Bella@Your weapon
Bella@Do you have a habit of hair removal?
You@Eat me clean
Bella@Is this okay?
You@Okay. I feel like you are really good at it.
Bella@Won't roar in pain
You@Quite comfortable
Bella@And it has no taste
Bella@Great
Bella@Normal boys, boys met in nightclubs
Bella@It's just that the smell will be a bit stronger.
Bella@you are really clean
You@That means you should look for me more often in the future.
Bella@That depends
Bella@What are the results of our research today?
You@Hurrah
Bella@Then shall we study yours first?
Bella@where is the sensitive zone
You@You are more experienced and you have the final say.
Bella@ok
You@You have a pretty good mouth, right?
Bella@Who just said that he wanted to learn something?
You@You really eat so deeply and feel comfortable
Bella@So you like this kind of thing
You@yes
Bella@Then what do you want to say?
Bella@Is this deep enough?
You@It’s almost been sucked out by you
Bella@Yeah
You@Is it because your skills are too good?
Bella@Am I that powerful?
Bella@Well, who knows if you are nice to me?